robocraftgame.com 2018-06-30

# ROBOCRAFT | Privacy Policy

23 May 2018

Freejam maintains this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) that summarizes our policies and processes for protecting the privacy of all personal information gathered from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to our website(s) or who download Freejam’s products and services, and when and how such information is collected, used, transferred, disclosed and safeguarded. This policy also explains how anyone can review, update, correct, or delete their personal information and specify what information, if any, they would like to receive from Freejam on an ongoing basis.

THE USER OF OUR SERVICES, GAMES, AND WEB SITES ARE SUBJECT TO AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. BY USING OUR SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED HEREIN WITH RESPECT TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. THIS PRIVACY POLICY ONLY ADDRESSES ACTIVITIES FROM OUR SERVERS. THIRD PARTY SITES (INCLUDING WHICH WE MAY LINK) AND THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS MAY HAVE THEIR OWN POLICIES, WHICH WE DO NOT CONTROL, AND THUS ARE NOT ADDRESSED OR CONTROLLED BY THIRD POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR SERVICES OR ACCESS OUR SITES.

Freejam is committed to ensuring your privacy and protecting the security of your personal information. This policy covers the Freejam public websites – [www.robocraftgame.com](http://www.robocraftgame.com/), [www.Cardlifegame.com](http://www.cardlifegame.com/) , [https://robocraftinfinity.com](https://robocraftinfinity.com/) – and all online forms, internal forms and means of communication on the Websites and in the computer game clients for Robocraft and Cardlife (hereinafter – “Game”) through which Freejam collects personal information.

If you do not agree with any terms of conditions described in this Policy or the Terms of Service, you may not use the Website or the Game.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Policy, please [contact Freejam](https://freejam.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/requests/new "Contact Freejam"). We will use reasonable efforts to respond to any email requests for information of assistance as soon as practicable.

## 2.1 Collecting Information

We or our business partners may collect and process the following types of information and/or data about you and/or associated such information with your personal information on our servers and will store them for as long as the data is necessary for proper functioning of the services and to serve your account:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time you register to use our Website and Game services, subscribe to our service, post material or requesting further services including your first name and last name, email address, social network ID, username and password. We may also ask you for any information (required for organizational activities) when you enter a competition or promotion sponsored by our business partners and when you report a problem with our Website of Game.

  * If you contact us we may keep a record of that correspondence.

  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders.

  * Details of your visits to our Website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

  * For some activities, we may ask you to create a username and password. In some cases your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographical information or information regarding your computer (capabilities, game data, processing, etc.) to Freejam. We may use this information to generate aggregate statistic about our user community and may provide such non-personal information to advertisers and/or our partners. In addition, Freejam may use such information for security, system integrity (the prevention of hacking, cheats, etc.), or enforcement purposes.

## 2.2 IP Address and Cookies

We or our business partners may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our partners. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computers hard drive and transmit certain information about your behaviour back to us. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us, for example:

  * To estimate our audience and usage pattern.

  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our Website according to your individual interests, as well as make your experience with Freejam more personal and pleasant.

  * To speed up your searches.

  * To recognize you when you return to our Website.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system may issue cookies when you log on to your Website.

## 2.3 Log Files

Like most internet services, we may also use log files on the server side. The data held in log files includes your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type, e-mail application, Internet service provider, referring/exit Web pages, computer platform type, date/time stamp, and user activity (e.g., feature usage, user rankings, game statistics). Freejam uses server log data to analyze trends, administer the services offered through the Website and in the Game.

The software enabling the Website and the Game has associated log and temporary files that are stored on Freejam’s servers. These files store your account information, preference settings, system notifications as well as other data necessary to enable you to participate on the Website and in the Game. Your information may also exist within regularly performed server backups. The foregoing information is collected on an aggregated and anonymous basis for providing the Website and Game functioning.

## 2.4 EAC and Anti-Cheat (Roboshield)

The Freejam games integrate the software EasyAntiCheat to protect against attempts to cheat in. The EasyAntiCheat software captures, stores and shares information used for the sole purpose of protecting Freejam games from cheating. EAC does not target nor store any data identifying individual users outside of their game user ID, HardwareID, and IP address. For full details on how EAC captures, stores and shares information please read Roboshield and EAC Privacy Details (<https://www.easy.ac/en-us/support/robocraft/account/privacy/>)

When you play any of the games and/or services offered by Freejam, or use any of the communication features on the Websites and in the Game, your IP address (the Internet protocol address from which you access any of the above) may be stored in our records. When any Game is updated or “patched”, our patch routine may check your computer to see that you have the most recent version of the game-specific files; when you communicate on the Website, within the Game or any other communication feature on the Website or within the Game (e.g. live chat, instant message services and the like), ever “privately” to another person, you do so with the understanding that those communications go through our servers, can be monitored by us, you have no expectation of privacy in any of those communications and, accordingly, you expressly consent to monitoring of communications that you send and receive.

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Freejam uses industry-standard technology, such as firewalls, in an effort to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Website of the Game, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

Generally, the information that you disclose on our website is collected by Freejam or by third parties such as co-sponsors or vendors for the promotion. Freejam’s use of any such information will be governed by this Policy. The names of third parties such as co-sponsors (other than vendors hired by Freejam to conduct, administer, and execute a promotion on behalf of Freejam) will be disclosed to you when you are asked to sign up for the promotion.

We generally do not sell or trade any personal information about our customers, prospects, or visitors to any third parties. We may share, however, aggregated demographic information with our business partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

Without your consent we are entitled to share the information stipulated in clause 2 “Collecting Personal Information” with third party companies that perform services, such as email delivery, hosting and payment processing, for the purpose of duly providing you with products and services of the Website and the Game that you request from us. However, these companies will generally only be entitled to use received information in order to provide the services of the Website and the Game that you request from us.

Finally, in the event Freejam combined with another company in the future through a corporate merger, sale, acquisition, liquidation or other similar process, your personal information may be transferred with the business or a part of it, or may be sold as an asset of the business.

Freejam strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Freejam intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an “adequate” level of protection for your Personal Information.

In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained. Additionally, in the unlikely event we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can, and you authorise us to, disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. Furthermore, Freejam may also disclose information about you in case Freejam determines that such disclosure is necessary for national security reasons, law enforcement and/or other public importance issues.

You also have the opportunity to subscribe to services for receiving e-mails (newsletters, Game – and Website – updates) that will be forwarded to your email address stipulated by you while registration.

If you opted-in to commercial marketing emails but no longer want Freejam to send you emails about our products and services, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email. Please note, however, that we may still contact you via email with questions or issues specific to your account.

If you have questions about our privacy practices, please, [contact Freejam](https://freejam.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/requests/new). We will use reasonable efforts to respond to any email requests for information of assistance as soon as practicable.

The accounts on Freejam associated Websites and games are available only to individuals who are not under the age of sixteen (16). If you are under the age sixteen (16), you may not create an account on the Website, you may not sign up for any subscription service or buy anything through the Website, and you are not eligible to enter any of our sweepstakes or promotions unless the holder of parental responsibility chooses to register an Account and give consent. Persons under 16 years of age should not use the Website of Game.

If you are the holder of parental responsibility and choose to register an Account for any freejam game on behalf of your child, the personal data of your child will be collected, processed and used. If your child is below the age of 16 years, consent must be given or authorised by you as the holder of parental responsibility.

Except as may be required by law, Freejam will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose any personal information from children 16 years of age or under without first having the holder of parental responsibility give consent. We take kids privacy seriously, and encourage parents to play an active role in their children’s online experience at all times.

Freejam recommends that parents and guardians spend time online with their children to become more familiar with the type of content available on the Internet, including our online games.

Parents and guardians should regularly oversee their children’s use of email and other online communications and transactional features. Control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers that can help provide a safe online environment for kids.

If you suspect we have inadvertently collected information about a child under 16, please [contact Freejam](https://freejam.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/requests/new) and we will promptly work to remove such information from our systems.

  * You may ask us to delete all stored personal data, which in some cases will lead to the termination of your account.
  * You may ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal information that we hold about you free of charge.
  * You may ask us for the categories of personal information that we hold/store.
  * You may ask us to provide you with copies of the personal information that we hold about you at any time. This may, in our discretion, be subject to a fee in accordance with a fee in accordance with applicable law.
  * Which business partners we may send the data to and what data we send to those business partners, in particular recipients in third countries or international organisations. (This is suggested but may not be required)

If you wish to pursue any of these choices, then please [contact us through Zendesk](https://freejam.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/requests/new)

Additionally, please be aware that if you opt-out of receiving commercial email from us or otherwise modify the nature or frequency of promotional communications you receive from us, it may take up to 30 days for us to process your request, and you may receive commercial email from us that you have opted-out from during that period.

This Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. If we make a material change to the Policy, we will notify you by posting the change on the Policy and, if necessary, give you additional choices regarding such change. Your continued use of our Website will signify your acceptance of these changes

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Policy, or have other questions or suggestions about our Website, please [contact Freejam](https://freejam.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/requests/new).
